export interface QuestionData {
  question: string;
  answer: string;
  category: string;
}

export const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question: '질문1',
    answer: '답변1',
    category: 'CS지식',
  },
  {
    question: 'HTML 질문2',
    answer: 'HTML 답변2',
    category: 'HTML',
  },
  {
    question: 'CSS 질문3',
    answer: 'CSS답변3',
    category: 'CSS',
  },
  {
    question: 'JS 질문4',
    answer: 'JS 답변4',
    category: 'JS',
  },
  {
    question: 'React 질문5',
    answer: 'React 답변5',
    category: 'React',
  },
  {
    question: 'Web 질문6',
    answer: 'Web 답변6',
    category: 'Web',
  },
  {
    question: '질문7',
    answer: '답변7',
    category: '프로젝트',
  },
  {
    question: '질문8',
    answer: '답변8',
    category: '기타',
  },
  {
    question: 'React 질문9',
    answer: 'React 답변9',
    category: 'React',
  },
  {
    question: 'Web 질문10',
    answer: 'Web 답변10',
    category: 'Web',
  },
  {
    question: 'CSS 질문11',
    answer: 'CSS 답변11',
    category: 'CSS',
  },
  {
    question: 'HTML 질문12',
    answer: 'HTML 답변12',
    category: 'HTML',
  },
  {
    question: 'React 질문13',
    answer: 'React 답변13',
    category: 'React',
  },
  {
    question: 'JS 질문14',
    answer: 'JS 답변14',
    category: 'JS',
  },
  {
    question: 'Web 질문15',
    answer: 'Web 답변15',
    category: 'Web',
  },
  {
    question: 'Web 질문16',
    answer: 'Web 답변16',
    category: 'Web',
  },
];
